iheartchaos.com 2017-09-22

# I HEART CHAOS — Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

I Heart Chaos takes the private nature of your personal information very seriously. This Privacy Policy (which we adapted from the Tumblr privacy policy) describes how we treat the information we collect when you visit and use the website available at iheartchaos.com (the “Website” or “IHC”) and is made available under the Creative Commons Sharealikelicense. Please read this notice very carefully.

Since IHC is currently hosted on Tumblr, [please also read the Tumblr privacy policy](http://www.tumblr.com/policy/en/privacy) as well.

 **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, I Heart Chaos collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. IHC’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how IHC’s visitors use its Website and for general traffic information. Information collected by IHC is separate from information collected by Tumblr, and the information IHC has access to is collected via Google Analytics and does not identify any user specifically.

 **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Tumblr discloses potentially personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on IHC’s behalf or to provide services available at the Website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Analytics information is not sold or rented to any third party for any reason.

 **Links to Third Party Sites**

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by IHC. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that IHC does not own or control, or employees that Tumblr does not manage. The Website contains links to third party websites and web applications via links in articles and around the site and via third party advertisments. Any information you provide to, or that is collected by, third-party sites may be subject to the privacy policies of those sites, if any. We encourage you to read such privacy policies of any third-party sites you visit. It is the sole responsibility of such third parties to adhere to any applicable restrictions on the disclosure of your personally-identifying information, and IHC and its affiliates shall not be liable for wrongful use or disclosure of your personally-identifying information by any third party.

 **Security**

All non-personally-identifying information, potentially personally-identifying and personally identifying-information described above is stored on Tumblr or Google servers.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tumblr uses cookies to help Tumblr identify and track visitors, their usage of the Tumblr Website, and their Website access preferences. Tumblr visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Tumblr Website, with the drawback that certain features of Tumblr’s Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

 **Address Book Data**

Any external address book data (email contacts, etc.) that a user voluntarily gives Tumblr access to will only be used for the described feature (looking up friends, etc.), and will not be stored or repurposed.

 **Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://t.umblr.com/redirect?z=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.networkadvertising.org%2Fmanaging%2Fopt_out.asp&t=NDBhYjdmYTE3MjkzODM4MGQ5YjczZGUzODk4NjlkZjBlZmYzN2Y5NSxUbU4zdWpESg%3D%3D&p=&m=0).

 **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, IHC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in IHC’s sole discretion. If we do then we’ll notify you by posting the amended policy on the Website or by emailing you of the nature of the modifications along with a link to the modified document so that you can review it. In all cases, use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected.

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us at cranberryzero@iheartchaos.com
